翻译：Forzatabitha
克里斯蒂安刚才维加斯回来
Christian just got back from vegas.
我只是周末去那儿办点私事
Yeah. It was just for the weekend. Private thing.
他认识每个人
He knows everyone.
"认识"，这年头谁能认识所有人？
"knows."who "knows" anyone these days?
比较像你在维加斯到处闲逛
More like you hang out when you're in vegas.
在维加斯你呆在哪？
So where did you guys stay in vegas?
我喜欢曼德勒的四季
I like the four seasons,the mandalay.
我喜欢最里面的位置
I like the end of the strip
因为我可以看着飞机飞入麦卡伦机场
So I can watch the planes fly into mccarran.
很高兴终于见到你了，伙计
Well, it's good to finally meet you, man.
你知道，最后终于可以亲自见到一个人很令人开心
It's good to finally, you know,meet the man in person.
呵呵
Yeah.
没问题
No problem.
嘿，我
And hey, I, um,
我真的想谢谢你给我那个角色
I really want to thank you for giving me that role.
不是我
I didn't give you that role.
你该谢谢你女朋友和导演
Your girlfriend and the director did.
是，但是我听说我不是第一人选
Yeah, but I heard I wasn't exactly gerald's first choice.
雷恩，行了，别这么说
Ryan, come on.Don't say that.
不，他说得对,你不是
No, he's right.You weren't.
但是我去找他告诉他这电影是我投资的
But I went to him and told him that I'm paying for this movie,
如果他不用我助手的男朋友
So if he doesn't put my assistant's boyfriend in it,
那么我就退出，这是他恐慌的
Then I'm pullin' out, and that's when the panic sets in.
恐慌？
Panic. Panic set in?
我是说这不过是一部低成本的恐怖片，克里斯蒂安
I mean, it's just a low-budget slasher movie, christian.
我不认为他们被你威胁到了
I don't think people were panicked by you.
我认为不管怎样他们能筹到钱
I think, you know, they could have found the money somehow,
但是你使一切变得更容易，对吗？
But you made it easier, right?
我得承认我有点惊慌
Well, I have to admit, actually I was a little bit panicked.
事实是我出钱了
Fact of the matter is I'm paying for this thing.
我从你们那听说他得到了那个角色
I heard from both of you that he was right for the part.
间接地我促成你得到你的角色
Yeah, indirectly I had something to do with you getting the role,
但是如果不是你解决了角色分配的问题
But if it wasn't for you helping out with the casting
说服我这个家伙
And convincing me that this guy was,
是最好的人选
You know, the best one for the role,
那你可能就得不到这个角色了
Then yeah, you probably wouldn't have the part.
我们要谢谢你的美味
And we thank you for the favor.
我觉得我们都做了正确的选择
I think we all made the right decision.
在她为我工作的这一年里
You know, in the year that she worked for me,
她从没提过她有男朋友
She never mentioned having a boyfriend.
谁说我没提过
That is not true! I did, too!
你没注意
You just weren't paying attention.
真的？
Really?
你们看起来很幸福
You guys look happy though.
当然，真的很幸福
Yeah, we are.Really happy.
当然
Yeah, really are.
你们呢？
And you guys?
你们多久见一次
How long have you two been seeing each other?
我告诉你，宝贝，一年，就像我们
I told you, baby, a year.Just like us.
是
Yeah.
距离产生美
I like to keep things loose,though.
我是说，我爱她
I mean, I love her.
上帝啊，她真美
God, she's gorgeous.
但是一点点复杂更有趣
But it's more fun to keep it a little complicated.
复杂？
Complicated?
克里斯蒂安，你干什么？你想说什么？
Christian, what are you doing?Where are you going with this?
就是简单，显然，宝贝
Just being transparent, baby.
让什么变得简单？
Being transparent about what?
你知道有个手机应用叫爱慕？
You know that phone app, amore?
有点像一个找女朋友的应用
It's kinda like a girlfriend finder.
哦，我不知道
Yeah-- I mean no.
这是个什么应用？
Wh-what does it do?
它让事情变得简单
It makes... Things simple.
确定的...分配
Certain... Assignations.
真的很容易
Just really easy.
有视频可以确定人们的相貌
You know, you get live video,make sure that people look
这样可以明确他们的长相
Exactly the way they do in their profiles.
分配...
Assignations for...
什么意思？
What is that?
意昧着见面，老兄
It means meetings, dude.
哦，见面是为了...
Oh! Okay.Meetings for...
性交
Hookups.
你知道，女孩，夫妻，无论什么人
You know, girls, coupleswhatever, man.
夫妻，真的吗？
Couples. Really?
是，夫妻，真的
Yes. Couples. Really.
我猜它就是，我不知道
I guess it's just, well,I don't know, I'm...
我比较传统
I'm just a more conventional guy.
这就是为什么你跟吉娜杂一起而我跟塔拉
Which is why you're with gina,and I'm with tara.
你不嫉妒吗？
And you don't get jealous?
嫉妒？
Jealous?
如果有其他人参与进来
Yeah. If there are other people involved, like guys.
大多数是女孩子，我不嫉妒
Well, it's mostly girls.And no, I do not get jealous
看着我的女人跟另一个少妇认识
Watching my girl hook up with another chick.
这个家伙是认真的吗？
Is this guy--is this guy for real?
你认真吗？他认真吗？
Are you for real?Is he serious?
不，我是说，我
No, no, man.I mean, I--
好吧，你比较厉害
Look, you're the man. I'm--
我只能努力追赶你
I-I was just trying to keep up with you.
伙计，一切靠信任，对不？
Look, man, it's all about trust,all right?
我相信她，她相信我
I trust her,she trusts me.
如果我们之间不存在那种信任，我就无法这么做
Maybe if that trust wasn't there, I couldn't handle it.
但是我们在一起很快乐
But since it is,we have a good time.
克里斯蒂安，我还在这呢
Christian,I'm sitting right here.
你什么意思，你无法解决什么？
What do you mean,you couldn't handle it?
你无法处理什么？
Couldn't handle what?
我知道你爱我使我信任你
The fact that I know you love me makes me trust you.
那使我们做的一切更加激情
That makes everything we do more intense.
抱歉，克里斯蒂安喜欢吓着别人
I'm sorry. Christian likes to shock people.
明白
I get it.
或者至少他试着这么做
Or at least he tries to.
这跟震惊到别人无关
This has nothing to do with shocking people.
我就是不爽守旧派的那些狗屁礼节
I'm just sick of the old school shit about fucking propriety,
规矩还有其他废话
Etiquette and all that crap.
你已经在我身边一年了
You've been around me for a year.
那些真他妈操蛋
It's just fuckin' annoying.
这就好像当你星期天在你的家庭晚饭时
It's like when you're at your family dinner on Sunday,
每个人都在撒谎，克里斯蒂安我想走
And everyone's just lying--christian, I want to go.
你能结账吗？我已经说过了
Can you get the fucking check?- I've ordered the check.
马上就好
It's comin'. It's on its way.
真的？多久？
Really?How long does it take?
快了，别着急
Mm. It's coming though.Don't worry about it.
克里斯蒂安在我忘记之前
Oh, christian,before I forget,
我得最终确认下月所有的房间
I'm finalizing all the rooms for next month.
你确定你会来？
Are you definitely sure that you're not gonna come?
我不可能去新墨西哥
Yeah, there's no way I'm going to new mexico
看着一群孩子被讨厌的魔鬼
And watch a bunch of kids get tortured and killed
虐待杀害在一间仓库里
By some pissed-off ghost in a warehouse.
另外，我得忙着制作我自己的电影
Besides, I'll be busy making my own little movies.
什么意思？
What do you mean,you make your own movies?
为什么我们要去那个该死的饭局
Why in the hell did we have to go to that damn dinner?
吉娜坚持的
Gina insisted.
另外我有一点想见见她的新男友
Plus I was kinda interested to see who her new dude is.
真他妈是个白痴，吉娜是个聪明女孩
What a fuckin' moron.Gina's a smart girl.
你肯定觉得她应该找个更好的
You'd think she could get with someone better
而不是个失败的演员
Than some loser actor.
你对他了解多少？
What do you know about him?
不了解
Nothing.
我甚至从没想过这电影会被制作
I never even thought this movie would get made.
吉娜竭尽全力让这件事情变为现实
Well, gina worked very hard to make sure it happened.
我甚至从来没读过剧本
I never even read the script.
我告诉吉娜墨西哥人或者无论是谁拿出资金
I told gina if the mexicans or whoever came up with the cash
我就会配合
That I would just match it.
你为什么不再参与，宝贝
Why aren't you involved anymore, baby?
你为什么曾经参与？
Why were you ever involved?
我爸爸烦我干涉我的生活
My father was on my ass about doing something with my life.
当我告诉他我在做一部电影时，他就不停的烦我
When I told him I was doing a movie, he got off my back.
你穿个袍子干嘛？男人在这里
Why are you wearing a robe?Guy's almost over here.
最近那些花花公子怎么了？
What's with all the dudes lately?
我不知道，某个阶段吧
I don't know.It's a phase.
我喜欢某人看待
I like the idea of someone looking at something
某些他们不能拥有的东西的观点
They can't have.
男人的事情，权利与控制
Guy thing.Power and control.
但是有时候他们有我
But sometimes they do have me.
就那两次而已，你看起来不在意
Just those two times.You didn't seem to mind.
今天晚上的餐桌上我无法相信你
I can't believe you at dinner tonight.
所有你告诉他们的
All that shit that you were telling them.
这就是为什么你变得有距离和暴躁？
Is that why you're being so distant and bitchy, huh?
你为什么在意
Why do you even fucking care?
只是我的助手和某个白痴演员
It's just my assistant and some dumb actor.
我不知道，我猜我想
I don't know. I guess I'd like to keep
让我的生活私密
Some parts of my life private.
我生活的某些方面私密
Some aspects of my fucking life private.
泰拉，没人再有完全私密的生活
Nobody has a private life anymore, tara.
那好，你跟你的医生说什么了？
Okay. What do you talk to your shrink about?
你见坎贝尔医生时你怎么说的？
What do you talk about when you see dr. Campbell?
我没有说
I don't tell dr. Campbell anything
我没告诉过你的任何事
That I wouldn't tell you.
那是谎话，你对我撒谎了
That's a lie. That's not true.You just lied to me.
你想知道什么？
What would you like to know?
我想知道你和坎贝尔医生说的什么
I want to know what you talk to dr. Campbell about.
我谈论我的家庭
I talk about my family.
我说我爸爸试图控制我的生活
I talk about my father trying to control my fucking life.
你他妈的觉得我该和他说什么？
What the fuck do you think I talk to him about?
我不知道，其他的女孩
I don't know.Other girls.
我比对待其他任何女孩都更认真地对待你
I'm more serious about you than I have been with any other girl.
希望你也这么对我
Hope you feel the same way about me.
克里斯蒂安，有人要过来了
Christian, there's a fucking guy coming over.
真的？
Really?
他在这，在路上
He's here.On his way down the driveway.
我说了我希望你也这么对待我
And I said I hope you feel the same way about me.
你今晚怎么了？晚饭上
What was with you tonight, hmm?At dinner.
你开始激动了？
You were so tense. Hmm?
让他进来
You let him in.
嗨，里德，对吗？
Hi. Reed, right?
快进来
Come on in.
我是泰拉
I'm tara.
这是里德
This is reed.
你好，我是克里斯蒂安
What's up, man?I'm christian.
嗨，伙计
Hey, man.
我想你已经见过泰拉了
I see you've met tara.
是
Yeah.
想来点喝的吗？龙舌兰酒
You want something to drink?Shot of tequila.
当然
Sure.
她很性感，对吗？
She's hot, right?
比你寄给我的照片还性感
Way hotter than the pics you sent me.
来一杯
Have a drink.
放松
Relax.
Be comfy, man.
你想看点更好的
You wanna see something better than that.
他怎么再次得到钱？
How does he have all that money again?
信托资金
Uh, trust fund.
他爷爷奶奶拥有近千颗橡树
His grandparents own like half of thousand oaks.
泰拉很漂亮，你不觉得？
She's beautiful, tara, don't you think?
她还好
She's okay.
别再去那了，宝贝，我可不会跟你去了
Don't go there, babe.I'm not doing that with you.
干什么？
Doing what?
比如像那个女孩比我美吗？
That whole "is that girl prettier than me?" thing you do.
我是说，你为什么问我？
I mean, why are you asking me that?
你甚至从没提起过她
Look, you never even mentioned her.
你从没告诉过我关于她的事
You never told me about her for a year.
你甚至连她的名字也没提过
You didn't even mention her by name.
仅仅是克里斯蒂安的女朋友
It was just"christian's girlfriend."
你也没告诉过我那人是怎样一个人渣
And you really didn't tell me what a douchebag that guy is.
天啊
Christ!
我从没提起过她因为我们从没真正一起逛过
The reason I never mentioned her is that we never really hung out
直到她开始在电影方面帮助我
Until she started helping me with the movie.
她为什么帮你？
Why was she even helping you out?
她太无聊了
She was bored.
除了购物和做爱她还需要做别的事
She needed something to do besides shopping and fucking.
我是说，乔恩和我做了大多数工作
I mean, jon and I did most of the work,
但是她还是有点作用
But she helped out a little,I guess.
她也在那个角色方面帮助了你
She did push you for the part.
我知道这可能是因为我和克里斯蒂安
I know it was probably a favor to me and christian,
但是没有她我不知道会发生什么？
But without her, I don't know what would've happened.
分配完角色后，她就消失了
And then after casting,she just disappeared.
她不再经过制片办公室
She just stopped coming by the production office.
我大概一个月没有见过她
I haven't seen her in like a month.
嗨
Hey.
谢谢
Thanks.
我告诉过你不要发短信给我
I told you not to text me.
为什么不行？
Why can't I text you?
因为他会看我电话
Because he looks at my phone.
为什么我们不能在我那见面
Why can't we meet at my place?
这种事不要再发生了
That's not gonna happen anymore.
那就是跟你在一起的人，上帝
So that's who you're with.Jesus.
你觉得你是谁
Who'd you think you were--
就是这个家伙给了你奔驰
So this is the guy that gave you the mercedes
用私人飞机载你去毛伊岛
And has a private jet and takes you to maui
住在马里布的房子里
And lives in the fucking mansion in malibu.
莱恩，求你别这样
Ryan, please.
上一晚杀了我
Last night killed me.
为什么？
Why?
因为我终于看到你跟他在一起
Because I finally saw you with him.
我知道你不如意
I know you better than he does.
你不开心，泰拉
You're not happy, tara.
谁说的？
Who said anything about happy?
他关心我，他爱我
He takes care of me,and he's in love with me.
这很重要
It's serious.
去他的，莱恩，谁开心，谁真正开心？
Fuck it, ryan. Who's happy? Who's really happy?
告诉我，吉娜
Tell me.Gina.
哦，当然.吉娜是这样，她很开心
Oh, of course.Gina is. Gina's happy.
另一个原因为什么我无法跟她相处
Right, another reason why I couldn't stand being around her.
你真的做了那些鬼事
And-- you really do all that shit?
找随便哪个家伙来操你？
Couples? Random guys fucking you?
上帝，泰拉，莱恩，别说了
Jesus, tara.Ryan, stop.
别再到处说了，好吗？
This isn't going anywhere, okay?
讨论这个没有意义
So there's no point in having this discussion.
必须结束，我们不能再这样做了
This has to end.We can't do this anymore.
你为什么现在才问我这一切？
Why are you asking me all this now?
因为我之前没见过他，我很在意
Because I hadn't met him before,and I do care.
我无时无刻不在想你，我不能自己
I think about you all the time.I can't help it.
这让我恶心
And it makes me sick.
我无法不让我自己想起他让你做的那些事
Can't get the things he makes you do out of my mind.
莱恩.你知道我怎么想的
Ryan-- how do you think I felt
看着他手机里那些照片
Watching him flashing pictures on his fucking phone
在我面前
In front of me?
上晚令我恶心，真他妈令人恶心
Last night made me sick.It made me fuckin' sick.
我们不能再这样了，该结束了
We can't do this anymore. This has gotta end.
结束什么？
What's gotta end, hmm?What?
最后四个星期操我吗？
Fucking me for the last four weeks?
你想结束
You wanna end that?
够了，莱恩
Stop, ryan.
你跟他说过我吗？你告诉过他
You ever tell him about me?Did you ever tell him
你三年前爱上我了吗？
That you fell in love with me three years ago?
你抛弃我当你发现
That you dumped me when you realized
我不是能帮你的那个人
I was the guy who might not make it,
你抛弃我
That you essentially abandoned me
就为了一个富有的人渣
For a bunch of rich douchebags?
现在这个混蛋呢？莱恩
And now that asshole?- Ryan!
你是谁，莱恩？你还是酒吧招待
Who are you, ryan?You're still bartending.
你仍然当兰德尔兼职助理
You're still working for randall as a part-time assistant
在一个破酒店
At a fucking hotel.
这个傻逼电影对你没有任何帮助
This dumb little movie's not going to do anything for you.
那你还帮我做什么？我不知道
Then why push me for it?- Oh, I don't know.
因为我在意你，知道你多么得到那个角色？
Because I care about you and knew how much you wanted it?
这就是我在说的，宝贝
See, that's what\ I'm saying, baby.
我太爱你了，宝贝，我们在一起时有很多欢乐
I loved you so much, baby.We had so much fun together.
你离开后我无法恢复
I never got over it when you left.
这要杀了我，我试着忘记的
It killed me, and I tried so hard to let it go.
我努力试着忘记
I tried so hard to let go of it.
就在我认为我已经习惯没有你时
And just when I think I'm gonna make it without you,
吉娜突然说起她老板的女朋友
Gina suddenly started talking about her boss's girlfriend
但是她描述的这个女孩完全不像你
But this girl she described didn't sound anything like you.
当我试镜时再见你
And then when I saw you at that audition...
我仍然爱着你
I'm still so in love with you.
我不想这样，但是没办法
I don't fuckin' want to be,but I am.
我现在跟他在一起
I'm with him now.I'm with him.
你怎么想的？
What are you thinking?
你觉得你会一直跟那个家伙在一起吗？
You think you're gonna nail this guy, move in with him?
你觉得那个混蛋会娶你吗？
You think that creep's gonna marry you?
莱恩，别说那些
Ryan, don't go there.
这对我也很困难
It's hard for me, too, okay?It's hard for me, too.
这就是为什么我在电影方面帮助你因为我在意你
That's why I tried helping you with the movie 'cause I care.
但是你不至于跟我说这些伤害我的话
But you don't have to go and say things that are gonna hurt me.
离开他，离开那个地方，做什么？
Leave him. Get out of there.- And do what?
我不知道，回到我身边，我们会有工作
I don't know. Come back to me. We'll get a job.
我们一起生活.然后呢，莱恩
We'll move in together.Get a job and do what, ryan?
你不记得那有多困难？
Do you not remember how hard we were busting our asses?
你不记得那些日子？
Do you remember those days?
不，等等，也许不是因为你还在经历那些事
No, wait. Probably not because you're still living them.
我不想再回到那种日子，莱恩
I'm not going back to that, ryan.
我不想再继续一次次的试镜
I'm not going back to going on auditions
我从来就不想找个工作
For jobs I'm never gonna get.
当个酒吧招待为了他妈的一小时八块钱
For bartending for 8 bucks a fucking hour.
我不会这么做
I'm not gonna do it.
你记得这对我们多艰难？
Do you remember how hard it was for us?
我们一文不值
We were always fucking broke.We were busting our asses.
我们连房租都付不起，莱恩
We couldn't even pay the fucking rent, ryan.
我们连他妈的房租都付不起
We couldn't pay the fucking rent.
这对我没有乐趣，我不想再这样
That wasn't fun for me.I'm not going back to that.
我需要有人来照顾我
And I need someone to take care of me.
我需要有人照顾我
And I needed someone to take care of me.
嗨
Hey.Hey.
来点喝的吗？
Want me to get you something to drink?
好啊，水
Yes. Water.
你怎么样？
Oh. How was your day?
还不错
It was fine.
你怎么不告诉你的生活？
Why don't you tell me about your day instead?
我起床，这个早上我上了两节瑜伽课
Okay. I got up, and I taught two yoga sessions this morning,
然后我去试镜
And then, oh, I went to that audition,
我上次告诉过你
You know, the one that I told you about last time.
太糟糕了
It was awful.
我肯定没有得到这个工作
I definitely didn't get the job,but whatever.
上帝，随后什莉打电话给我
Oh, my god, and then sheely called me,
她开始告诉我这个家伙的一切
And she started telling me all about this guy.
该死，什么？
Goddamn it!What?
怎么了？
What's wrong?
你为什么那么做？
Why the fuck did you do that? Why?
我只是和你进入状态了
I just get into it with you, okay?
对不起，我无法控制自己
I'm sorry.I can't help it.
看着...
Look...
这样就是这样
This... Is just this.
什么意思？
What does that mean?
我认为你性感
I think you're hot.
我有兴趣
I have fun.
但这无法改变我的情况
But it's not changing my situation.
究竟发生什么了？
Okay, what's really going on here?
我觉得泰拉去见了某人
I think tara's seeing somebody.
上帝
Oh, jesus.
克里斯蒂安，这有关系吗？
Christian, what does that even mean, okay?
想想你们做的
Considering what you guys do.
我是说，你在意吗？
I mean, do you even care?
我在意，很在意
Yes, I care.I care a lot.
你觉得她骗你？
What, you think she's cheating on you?
她那晚真的表现的很奇怪
She was acting really, really strange at dinner last night.
我不知道为什么
I couldn't figure out why.
今早她去跟某人见面喝咖啡
And then today she met some guy in the morning for coffee.
就是，她...
It's just, she-okay.
你怎么知道的
I mean, how do you know that she met someone?
她跟你说了？没有
What, did she tell you?No.
那就是那个人告诉你了？
Okay, did--what, did the guy tell you?
不是
No.
今天我还有点事要做
I've got some stuff I have to do today.
你最好离开
I think you better leave.
我不认为你应该再回来
And I don't think you should come back here.
为什么？
And why's that?
我无法处理这种情况
I can't handle this anymore.
要现金吗？
Need some cash?
不，克里斯蒂安
No. Christian,I don't need any cash.
快点出去
Just-- just get out.
别这样，辛西娅
Come on, cynthia.
滚
Get the fuck out.
滚出去
Get the fuck out of here!
很抱歉我没有祝贺你
I'm really sorry that I didn't congratulate you
开始了你自己的公司
On starting your own pr company.
那一定很刺激
I mean, that must be really exciting.
不用急着祝贺我，还没真正开始
Don't congratulate me just yet.It hasn't really taken off.
但是要不是克里斯蒂安
But you know,if it wasn't for christian
我永远开不了公司
I'd never have been able to start it.
克里斯蒂安很有帮助
Yeah. Christian can be very helpful that way.
上晚的晚餐很有趣了
So dinner was fun last night.
抱歉如果我看起来不在状态
I'm sorry if I, you know,seemed out of it and such.
我只是被一些事情困扰着
I was just really preoccupied with things.
我知道克里斯蒂安
I know how christian gets.
我不得不说莱恩被他吓到了
And I have to say that ryan was a little shocked by him.
但是他真的喜欢他，他觉得他很不错
But he really liked him.He thought he was a great guy.
真的吗？
Oh, really? He did?
觉得他很好
Yeah.Thought he was really cool.
你知道，这年头很少能见到喜欢的人
You know, good guys are really hard to come by these days,
你是个幸运的女孩
So you're a very lucky girl.
- Tell me about it.
我不能相信我发现了如此真实的人
I can't believe I actually found someone so genuine.
他很好
He's a great guy.
这很不错
Look, this was nice.
我...
I just, um--
抱歉，我只是想知道点什么
I'm sorry. I just wanted to know something.
什么？
What?
你为什么离开那个电影
Why are you off the movie?
你不会去新墨西哥对吗？
I mean, you're not coming to new mexico, right?
是，我不能
Oh, no. Yeah, I can't.No, I can't do that.
我只是很好奇因为我做好了一切
I'm just curious because I'm finalizing everything,
我不明白，一个月前你看起来对此还很感兴趣
And, I don't know, you just seemed so into it a month ago.
我是说..
Yeah, I mean...
告诉我
Okay, tell me something.
你真的喜欢电影吗？
Do you really like movies?
当然
Yeah!
很喜欢？当然
Really, really like movies?Of course!
上一次去电影院看电影什么时候？
When's the last time you went to see a movie in the theater?
一部真正对你有意义的电影？
A movie that you really thought meant something to you?
我们去了上周的首映
We went to the premiere last week--
不是首映，这不算
Not premieres.Premieres don't really count.
我不明白
I don't know, you know.
我猜它不会再困扰我了
I guess maybe it's just not my thing anymore.
我也不想离开克里斯蒂安
And plus I don't wanna be away from christian
我猜我会一直跟他在一起
For that long, I guess.
我明白
I get it.I totally get it.
我也不会离开莱恩
I wouldn't want to be away from ryan for that long either.
那时我无聊
No, it's just, at the time I was bored,
我需要做些事
And I needed something to do.
所以我参与其中
And so that's why I got involved, and...
现在我想找些其他的事来做
You know, now I'm looking for something else to do, so...
你好吗？
Are you okay?
我只是
Yeah, I'm just--
有太多事
I just have a lot of stuff going.
我心事重重的
I'm so preoccupied and...
我得走了
Look, I really have to go.
等等，我来
Wait! Stop.It's on me.
我可以记到制作费用上
I can bill it to the production.
真的，泰拉
Seriously.Tara, it's okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
见到你真高兴，吉娜，过一阵再聊
Good seeing you, gina.Um, we'll talk soon.
拜
Bye.
拜，泰拉
Bye, tara.
我刚跟她吃过午餐
So I just had lunch with her
什么事也没有
Nothing.
她说的都是你的好
She said really nice things about you.
她有点紧张但是没什么
I mean, she seemed a little tense, but nothing.
她不会去新墨西哥因为她说她会想你
She's not coming to new mexico because she said she'd miss you.
真的？
Really?
克里斯蒂安，我纳闷
Christian，I'm just wondering.
你觉得她会跟我说什么？
What did you think she was gonna say to me?
没什么，宝贝，碰运气
Nothing, babe.I just want the chance
你们两个保持联系
For the two of you to reconnect.
我挂了，之后再聊
I gotta go.I'll talk to you later.
办公室见
Uh, okay.I'll be at the office.
好，宝贝
All right, babe.See you there.
非常好，性感
Oh, very good. Sexy.
保持
Yeah. Keep it.Ha ha.
抬起下巴
Pick up your chin.
非常好，微笑
Yes, very good. Smile.
手往上来点姿势
Muscle up. Come on.Give me some attitude.
很好，轮廓
That's good. Profile.
下巴低一点，很好
Lower the chin.Very good.
比利，转换灯光
，Billy, switch the lights.
他真棒
He's pretty cute.
莱恩，就位
Ryan, on your mark.
你叫莱恩对吗？
Hey, ryan.That's your name, right?
就位
Right. Get on the mark.
很好，保持
Good. Keep it right there.
很好
Okay.
是，一个月
Yeah, a month. Yeah.
但是赞德说他会找人替代我
But zander said he would find someone to take my place
直到我回来
Just until I got back.
不，杰夫，赞德说他可以给我换班
No, jeff, zander said it was cool if he gave me his shifts.
杰夫
Jeff!
杰夫，别这样，我需要现金
Jeff, come on, man.I just really need the cash.
如果你想要我求你，不可能
If you're gonna make me beg,then fuck it.
回见
I'll see you later. Bye.
我去了.好
I'm gonna head on up.All right.
谢谢
Thanks, man.
我们也在处理里奥的事
We're also handling the leo event,
我得挂了，莱恩来了
Listen, I gotta go.Ryan's here.
我知道不是
I know it isn't.
我觉得我们一起找出原因
Yeah, I think we're all about to find out why.
再见
Later.
甚至是他休息的日子
Ah! Even on his day off,
见到我最喜欢的助手真开心
It is always a pleasure to see my favorite assistant.
谢谢你第一次的赞美
Thanks, randall, for the first and only compliment
我今天准备接受
I'm going to receive today.
对不起，你咋了？
Oh, I'm sorry.What's wrong?
我只是
I-I was just, uh--
我试着换班
I was just trying to get extra shifts at the bar,
但是杰夫不同意
But jeff's being a prick.
我能帮什么忙
Well, what can I do to help?
我想知道这里是否
Well, I was wondering if there was anything else
有我能做的其他事
I could do around here.
你知道，当我给你这份工作时，它就是全职的
You know, when I offered you this job, it was full-time.
我知道
I know, I know.
但是允许你把它当做兼职工作因为你想这样
But I let you make it part-time because you wanted it that way.
兰德尔，我想去新墨西哥一个月
Randall, I'm going to new mexico for a month.
他们几乎支付了所有让我去完成这部电影
They're barely paying me anything to do this movie.
我真的需要现金
I really need the cash.
我能问你点事吗？
Can I ask you something?
你曾经考虑过...我不知道
Have you ever considered--I don't know.
为未来做一个长远计划
Making plans for a sustainable future?
嗯
Hmm?
我该怎么做？
What am I gonna do with you?
你真的很好，兰德尔
You've been really cool,randall.
我真的，你知道
I really, you know--
你知道我有多感激你为我做的
You know how much I appreciate what you've done for me.
你知道当你回来
You know you'll have this job waiting for you
会有工作等着你
When you get back.
你知道，对吗？
You know that, right?
至少你会有这份工作
You'll have this, at least.
我身无分文
I'm so strapped.
咋了？
What is it?
我完全忘了我还有约会
Oh, man, I totally forgot I have this appointment.
当然你得去赴约
Yeah, of course you did.
明天见，莱恩
Well, I will see you tomorrow, ryan.
我会看看我能为你做点什么
And I'll see what I can find for you.
谢谢，兰德尔
Thanks, randall
别担心，宝贝
Shh. Don't worry, baby.
会变好的
Gonna be all right.
Gonna be okay.
他在里面？是
He in?Hey. Yeah.
让我告诉他..替我留意着
Let me just tell him-keep an eye on that for me.
好的
Oh--
嗨，克里斯蒂安
Hey, christian.
别让女孩们进来
No girls allowed.
嗨，克里斯蒂安
Hey, christian.
那是什么？
What's that?
看看预算允许的特效
Going over effects the budget will allow.
虽然我男朋友是特效总监
Even though my boyfriend is the effects supervisor,
但是他不免费，所以我们得挑选
He's not doing this for free,so we have to pick and choose.
小婊子
That little bitch
我想跟你谈点事
I wanna talk to you about something.
嗯？
Yep?
什么？
What is it?
莱恩
Ryan.
又是一个我男朋友讨厌的话题
Another topic my boyfriend loves to hate.
真的？为什么？
Really? Why's that?
我制作的每一部电影
Every movie I've produced,
他都觉得我想上男主演
He thinks I'm trying to bang the leading man,
大部分时候，他是错的
And, uh, half the time,he's been wrong.
我想让你明天给莱恩打电话
I want you to call ryan in tomorrow.
告诉他他被换了
Tell him he's been replaced.
什么？为什么？
What? Why?
发生啥了？杰拉尔德什么问题？
What happened? What's gerald's problem?
跟杰拉尔德无关
This has nothing to do with gerald,
莱恩事实上不会被替换
And ryan's not actually being replaced.
不明白
I don't get it.
给莱恩打电话告诉他
Just call ryan in and tell him
杰拉尔德想把他踢出去
That gerald's thinking of taking him out of the movie.
你，乔恩，可以说服他
And you, jon, can convince him otherwise
如果莱恩愿意为你做点什么
If ryan's willing to do something for you.
比如什么？
Like what?
告诉他如果跟你睡觉他才能得到角色
Tell him he gets to keep the part if he sleeps with you.
为什么我得这么做？
Why the hell would I do that?
帮我个忙
Favor to me.
你没开玩笑？
You're not joking, huh?
我没有
No, I am not.
克里斯蒂安，我跟吉娜是朋友
Christian,I'm friends with gina.
莱恩完全就是个直男
Ryan is totally straight.
真的吗？
Really?
你觉得他是直男？
You think he's totally straight?
是，我这么认为
That's what I believe, yeah.
那他怎么得到酒店那份工作？
So how did he get the job at the hotel, huh?
因为他太直了，或者因为他太聪明了？
'cause he's so straight or 'cause he's so, um, smart?
克里斯蒂安，我跟吉娜是最好的朋友
Christian, I'm best friends with gina,
我不能这么对她
And I can't do this to her.
乔恩
Jon, jon, jon.
放松
Relax.
一个玩笑而已
It's just a prank.
测试莱恩，看看他的反应
Test ryan, see what his reaction is.
之后，你可以告诉他这只是个玩笑
Afterwards, you can tell him it's a joke.
如果他去告诉吉娜
And if he has the balls to go to gina
告诉她你的玩笑
And tell her about your little prank,
那你就说，克里斯蒂安让我这么做的
Then just say,"christian put me up to it."
全怪到我头上，我承担全部责任
Blame it on me.I'll take full responsibility.
克里斯，我不认为我能这么做
Chris, I don't think I can do this.
乔恩，这里有很多人
Jon, there are a lot of people in this town
可以称他们为制片人
Who call themselves producers.
你只是其中之一
You're just one.
好吧
Okay.
好
但是我仍然不理解
But I still don't get it.
你不需要明白
You don't need to.
另外，你可能得到一些运气
Besides, you might get lucky.
嘿，泰拉
Hey, tara!
宝贝
Baby!
嗨
Hi.
你今天干什么？
What'd you do today?
我去健身房了，哪一个？
I went to the gym.Which gym?
二分点，我是那的会员
Equinox.The gym that I'm a member of.
西好莱坞那的还是日落那的
The one on westwood or the one on sunset?
西好莱坞那的
The one in west hollywood.
你为什么去那家
Why'd you go to the one in west hollywood?
因为那距我见吉娜吃午餐的地方近
Because it was closer to where I was meeting gina for lunch.
你什么时候去的？
What time did you go to the gym?
告诉我，你觉得吉娜迷人吗？
Tell me something,do you find gina attractive?
不，我不会雇我觉得迷人的助理
No. I'd never hire an assistant I find attractive.
为什么不？她很漂亮
Why not? She's a pretty girl.
你觉得莱恩迷人吗？
Do you find ryan attractive?
好，我们开始吧
Okay, here we go.
不，我不觉得
No, I don't.
我觉得你在某些层面觉得他很迷人
Well, I figured you have to find him attractive on some level.
你让他当了电影的主角
You cast him as the lead in the movie.
不，不，那不是真的
No, no, that's not true.
我没有
I did not cast him in the movie.
好吧，你使我让他当上了主角
All right, you made me cast him as the lead in the movie.
不，我们跳过这个，我没让你做任何事
No, we've been over this. I didn't make you do anything.
你雇他因为帮吉娜个忙
You hired him as a favor to gina,
这就是为什么能演这部电影，不是吗？
And that's why he's in the movie, isn't it?
你会跟他做爱吗？
Would you fuck him?
你他妈的在问我什么？
What did you just fucking ask me?
我说，你会跟他做爱吗？
I said would... You... Fuck... Him?
不，我不会
No... I... Wouldn't.
过往的演员，我有两个给他们
Did actors in the past, and I have two words for them:
再也不会
Never again.
我觉得也许你们两个认识呢
I just thought maybe you two knew each other.
也许你们之前见过
Maybe you met before.
什么时候，我们之前什么时候见过
When? When would we have met before?
求你，放过我吧
Please, enlighten me.
也许是你当模特的时候
Maybe your modeling days when you first got to la.
上帝，不，克里斯蒂安，我没有
Oh, god, no, I hadn't, christian.
但是谁知道？
But you know, who knows?
那些日子我完全荒废掉了
I was pretty wasted during those days.
所以一切都有可能，对吗？
So anything's possible, right?
别这样
Come on.
克里斯蒂安，你为什么问我这些事
Christian, why are you asking me these things?
没有原因，你自我保护意识太强
No reason. You're the one getting all defensive.
我很寒心，宝贝
I'm chill, baby.
你为什么问我莱恩
Why are you asking me about ryan?
我只是觉得你们两个之前见过
I just thought maybe the two of you had met before.
没有，我们没有
No. Nope.We had not.
我们之前没见过
We had not met before.
我想再来一杯，你想要吗？
I'm gonna get another.You want one?
好
Yeah.
审问完了，给我来双倍的
After that interrogation,give me a fucking double.
你怎么样？
How was your day?
你今天去健身房了吗？
Did you go to the gym today?
嗨，宝贝
Hey, babe!
嗨，宝贝，怎么样？
Hey, babe.How'd it go?
我觉得我没成功，太多其他人了
Uh, I don't think I got it.Too many other guys.
抱歉，宝贝
I'm sorry, babe.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
克里斯蒂安跟辛西娅做瑜伽？
Christian does yoga with cynthia gray?
什么？
What?
我看了他的计划
I'm just looking at his schedule.
你认识她？
Do you know her?
我跟她一起上过表演课
Yeah. Actually, I was in an acting class with her
几年前
A few years ago.
再见她的名字觉得不可思议
Weird to see her name again.
那她现在在教瑜伽
So she's teaching yoga now.Typical.
是，那就是克里斯蒂安在做的
Right, that's exactly what christian's doing
当他跟辛西娅一起，就是瑜伽，当然
When he's over with cynthia. It's yoga. Sure.
我今天跟泰拉吃午餐了
So I had lunch with tara today.
是吗？是
You did?Yeah.
你还好吗？
You okay?
是，我只是
Yeah. Yeah, I just--
我不知道，我猜我有点惊讶
I don't know. I guess I'm a little surprised
在你昨晚告诉我她的事后
After what you told me about her last night.
我知道，但是克里斯蒂安让我去
Yeah, I know, but christian asked me to go, so--
为什么？我不知道
Why?I don't know.
像是他想我去发现什么东西
It was like he wanted me to find out something.
比如什么？我真的不知道
Like what? I really don't know.
之后，只是证实了他早已知道的一切
Afterwards, it just confirmed everything he already knew,
就是她不想再跟
Which is that she doesn't wanna have anything more
这部电影有什么关系
To do with the movie.
她还说什么了？
What else did she say?
我不觉得她相信我
Well, I don't think she believed me
当我告诉她你觉得克里斯蒂安很好
When I told her you thought christian was cool.
你为什么告诉她？
Why would you tell her that?Huh?
你为什么说我觉得克里斯蒂安很好
That-- why would you say that I thought christian was cool?
有什么关系？你不在意的，对吗？
What does it matter? You don't care that I said that, right?
莱恩？
Ryan?
你可以随时给她打电话只要你想，宝贝
You can tell her whatever you want, babe.
我是说，我甚至不认识她
I mean,I don't even know her.
她看起来也
She also seemed--
我不知道，她似乎很害怕
I don't know,she seemed scared.
真的很焦虑
Really anxious.
她有点让我想起
She kinda reminded me of like one of those girls
那些在电影里被跟踪的女孩
In those movies that's being followed by somebody.
我不知道，就是很奇怪
I-- I don't know.It was just very weird.
嗨，一切还好吗？
Hey!Hey. Is everything okay?
我意思是，你说我们不能再电话里说
I mean, you said we couldn't talk about this on the phone.
我问吉娜怎么了
I asked gina what this was about.
她也不知道，莱恩，好着呢
She had no idea.Ryan, it's okay.
把门关上
Close the door.
为什么？
But why?
这没人
Uh, there's no one here.
把门关上，莱恩
Close the door, ryan.
我们能快点吗？
Can we make this fast?
如果没什么我站着就好
I'd rather just stand,if that's okay.
究竟发生什么了？
What's going on?
为什么你让我晚上11点
Why are you calling me to the office
来办公室，乔恩？
At 11:00 at night, jon?
我直说了
Look, I'll be upfront.
杰拉尔德仍然对你当主角有异议
Gerald is still having problems with you for the lead.
我知道你知道这些
I know you've known this,
即使你已经正式出演
And even though you've been officially cast for this,
他仍可以重新考虑
He's reconsidering.
你在跟我开玩笑
You're fucking kidding me.
我没有开玩笑
No. I'm not fucking kidding you.
什么意思？
What does this mean?
重新考虑什么意思？
What does "reconsidering" mean?
我们一个月后就开机了，我投入我整个的生活
We're shooting in a month, jon.I put my whole life on hold.
坐下
Sit down.
我跟直接决定的克里斯和杰拉尔德是一起的
I'm the one with the direct line to chris and gerald.
告诉吉娜了吗？
Has gina been told about this?
还没有
No, gina hasn't been told about this.
如果还没有告诉吉娜，为什么我会在这
If gina hasn't been told about this, then why am I here?
我给她打电话
I'm calling her.
不用，把电话拿走
No, don't. Put the phone away.
莱恩，把电话放下
Ryan, put the phone down!
我可以保证你的角色
I can make sure you keep the role.
嗯？
Yeah?
怎么保证
How's that?
我打算去
Well, I'm going out to, uh,
棕榈泉褶这周末
Palm springs this weekend,and, uh...
你为什么不来？
Well, why don't you come?
你不跟比利去吗？
Aren't you going with billy?
不
No.
你是说我和吉娜
You mean me and gina?
不，只是
No. Just, um...
我和你
Just me and you.
当然，为什么不行，但是
Sure. Why not? But...
为什么等着？
Why wait?
说具体点
Exactly.
我们现在就开始吧
Let's do it now.
可以吗？可以
Yeah?Yeah.
现在就口交
Suck me off right now.
就在这，现在，办公室
Right here. Now.In the office.
确定？是
Yeah?Yeah.
快点，来吧，快把它放到你嘴里
Come on. Get to work.Fuckin' put it in your mouth.
认真的？
Seriously?
认真的，来吧
Seriously. Come on.
我需要脱裤子，硬起来
I need to get off.Make it hard.
这是你想要的吗？
Is this what you want?
口交吧，你知道你想要
Suck me off right now.You know you want it.
嗨，辛西娅
Hey, cynthia?
我是苏西沃特尔表演课的莱恩
Hey, uh, this is ryan from suzie walter's acting class.
是，我知道，很久了
Yeah, yeah, I know. It's-it's been a long time.
听着，我想问你点事
Listen, I wanted to ask you something.
这是谁？
Who is this?
我出去一下，安布尔给我发短信了
I'm going out.Amber texted me.
我们去喝一杯或者看电影或者干些其他的
We're gonna have a drink or see a movie or something.
很好
Cool.
真的？就这样？
Really? That's it?
你不会问我我去哪或者我什么时候回家
You're not gonna ask me where I'm going or when I'll be home?
什么都不问？
Nothing?
不，我相信你，宝贝
No. I trust you, baby.
好
Okay.
我先洗澡
I'm gonna take a shower first.
我出去了，一会就回来
Okay. I'm going out. I'll be back in a bit.
好
Okay.
你打算做什么？
What are you gonna do?
上网
Go online.
找点人来这里当你回来
Look for somebody to be here when you get back.
好，真的吗？今晚？
Oh, okay.Really? Tonight?
是，真的
Yeah. Really.
好
Okay.
你问起来很香
You smell nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨，是我
Hey, it's me.
我要你现在过来
I need you to come over now.
那，你记得我？不，我不记得
So, you remember me?No, I don't.
我过去常约克里斯蒂安，你知道，在我遇见你之前
Yeah, I used to date christian, you know, before I met you.
很好，你看起来一点也不惊讶
Great.You don't seem surprised.
老实说，我不在乎谁跟克里斯蒂安约会
Honestly, I don't really care who christian dated.
为什么我要惊讶？
And why would I be surprised?
在我之前，克里斯蒂安跟很多女孩出去
Christian went out with a lot of girls before me,
我不在乎
And I don't care.
我会，我在意
Well, I would.I would care.
辛西娅
cynthia...
真的没有线索吗？
Really don't have a clue,do you?
你不知道我和克里斯蒂安的一切吗？
You don't know anything about me and christian, do you?
那好，你知道什么
All right, you know what?
说出来，宝贝，我现在陷入什么问题
Lay it out, babe. What kind of trouble am I in?
泰拉，你知道，我有很多方法
Tara, you know,I have enough of a clue
跟你联系
To get into contact with you.
因为我觉得你需要走出这段关系
Okay, because I think, you need to get out of this relationship.
我觉得你需要离开他
I think you need to get away from him.
真的吗？
Really?
为什么？
Why?
因为他令人恶心
Because he's sick.He's a sick little boy.
继续
Go on.
我意思是，即使他和其他女孩乱搞
I mean, even though he was,you know, fucking other girls,
我们一起做过很多“连接”
There were, of course, the hookups that we did together.
我从来不想，我是说，他
I never wanted to.I mean, he...
强迫我做那些
Always pressured me into them.
真的？你不想？
Really? You didn't want to?
我确信，他和你做了同样的事
I'm assuming he does the same thing with you.
赶紧说完你的故事，辛西娅
Just finish your fucking story,cynthia.
我需要离开这
I need to get the hell outta here.
不真是个故事，不
Not really a story. No.
就在那一刻当一切对我变得清晰
Just that moment when everything became clarified for me.
有一晚当事情失控
You know, one night when things got out of hand.
怎么失控？
How?
我发现我自己在急诊室
I found myself in the emergency room at ucla.
什么情况？
Hmm. How did that happen?
克里斯蒂安决定请一群家伙来家里
Christian decided to invite a bunch of guys over to the house.
你允许了
And you let him.
没有
No.
事实上，我昏倒了
Actually, I didn't.I was passed out.
那是谁的错，辛西娅
And who's fault was that, cynthia, hmm?
你的宝贝克里斯蒂安决定弄碎
Your precious christian decided to crush up
很多rufelin到他给我的饮料里
A bunch of rufelin in a drink that he gave me.
首先，我从来不叫他可爱的
I never called him "precious,"first of all.
我相信那是你的名字
I believe that was your name.
第二，那是迷幻药
Secondly, it's "rohypnol."
第三，你知道我什么意思
Third of all--you know what I meant.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
真的
Really.
你不相信
You don't.
你想说什么，辛西娅？
So what are you saying, cynthia? What are you saying?
你想说你不想让你自己被群交
You saying that you didn't let yourself get gang banged,
你失控了，他录下了整个过程
That you had no control--he filmed the entire thing,
然后他威胁要把这个放到不同的地方
And then he threatened to put it up on different sites
如果我对任何人说了
If I said anything to anybody.
很明显你没有控制克里斯蒂安，我不一样
Obviously you weren't in control of christian. I am.
我告诉你是因为我觉得他要伤害你
I'm telling you this because I think he's gonna hurt you
用同样的方法
In the same way.
不，你告诉我因为你嫉妒
No, you're telling me this because you're jealous
也有点喝醉了
And a little drunk.
上帝，这真是女孩做的事
God, it's such a girl-thing to do.
克里斯蒂安不会伤害我
Look, christian's not gonna hurt me.
如果有，那我就是要伤害他的那一个
If anything, I'm the one that's gonna hurt him.
她在回来的路上
She's on her way back.
我们有20分钟
We got 20 minutes.
我们现在进入莱恩的脸书页面
We are now hacking into ryan's facebook page
因为你必须和他成为朋友
Because you have to be friends with him to look at it.
个人保护开着，照片被锁了
And privacy block is on,photos locked.
她跟他是朋友？
Is she friends with him?
不是
No.
你确定
Are you sure?
老兄，我已经当你的技术伙伴三年了
Dude, I've been your tech guy for like three years.
这个偏执狂怎么了？我从没见过你这样
What is up with the paranoia?I've never seen you like this.
停
Stop.
克里斯蒂安，你想我检查电话吗？
Christian, uh, you wanted me to check the phone?
我发现了那些你想让我看的已经删掉的短信
Think I found those deleted texts you wanted me to see.
不是很多，但是
Um, not a lot of them, but, uh,
我不知道这是什么意思，但是它被发给
I don't know what this means,but it was sent to...
被发送到莱恩的手机上
It was sent to ryan's phone.
你多快能进入他的银行账户？
How quickly can you hack into his bank account?
那是谁？
Who was that?
谁？
Who?
刚走出屋子的那个人
The guy that just walked out of the house.
你到底觉得我跟谁聊天？
Who in the fuck do you think I'm talking about?
他给我带了些海草
Oh, he brought me some weed.
你是个骗子
You're such a liar.
我怎么就成骗子了？
How does that make me a liar?
不仅仅是这些
It's not just that.
安布尔怎么样？
How was amber?
我上哪知道，我没见安布尔
I wouldn't know.I didn't see amber.
你没有，没有
You didn't? Nope.
你去哪了？
Where'd you go?
谁是辛西娅？
Who's cynthia?
我不知道你在说谁
I don't know who you're talking about.
别骗人了，克里斯蒂安
Stop fucking lying, christian.
我认识很多辛西娅，我意思是
I know lots of cynthias.What I meant was
我不知道你说的是哪个
I don't know which cynthia you're referring to.
很好
Fine. Okay.
有人发短信给我因为他们想跟我谈论你
Someone texted me because they wanted to talk to me about you.
结果是某个你在东边约过的女孩
Turns out that it's some girl you dated on the east side,
你不仅把她送进了医院
And not only did you put her in the hospital,
你也请了一群家伙来这
But you invited a bunch of fucking guys over
然后她被群奸，克里斯蒂安
And then pulled a fucking train on her, christian.
我知道整件事，等等
I know the whole thing.Wait, wait, wait, wait.
那根本就没发生过！克里斯蒂安，什么鬼？
That didn't fucking happen!Christian, what the fuck?
我确定，不，听着
Oh, right, I'm sure.No, look.
在你之前我约过叫辛西娅的女孩
I dated a girl named cynthia before you...
现在你想起来了
Now you remember.
但是那种事从没发生过
But none of that other shit happened.
好吗？
All right?
你就是个骗子
You're such a fucking liar.
我向上帝发誓
I swear to god!
如果有，我会告诉你
If it happened,I would tell you.
根本就没有这回事
It didn't fucking happen.
我不知道她为什么这么说
I don't know why she would say that.
我不知道，我也一样
I have no fucking clue. Me either!
我也不知道她为什么这么做
I don't know why she would say that either.
她在犯毒瘾，她很迷恋我
She's fucking on drugs,and she's obsessed with me.
我不知道怎么了，我不知道
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with-- I-I don't know.
她吸哪种毒，催眠药？
What kind of drugs was she on? Roofies?
我不知道，她疯了，我他妈不知道
I have no idea. She's crazy. I don't fucking know.
她也许嫉妒我跟你在一起而不是她
She probably is jealous that I'm with you instead of her.
但是真没有这回事，她吸毒
But it did not happen.She's on drugs.
是
Yes.
如果有，我会告诉你
If it happened,I would tell you.
我发誓
I swear to god.
但是真没有，谢谢
But it did not.Oh. Thanks.
真没有，我发誓
It didn't though.I swear.
好
Okay
谁？
Who's that?
没谁
Nobody. It's... Whoever.Nobody.
克里斯蒂安，是谁？
Christian, who is that?
就是我请到这来的人
It's just somebody I invited over,
但是我们可以选在另一晚
But we can do it another night.
我们可以取消
It's fine.We can cancel.
不，让他们来
No. Tell 'em to come over.
你确定？我是说，他们很近，但是
Are you sure? I mean, they're close, but...
不，不用取消
No. Don't cancel.
你去哪？
Where you going?
告诉他们来楼上见我
Tell 'em to meet me upstairs.
好吗？
Yeah?
他们想先用泳池.好，随便
They wanna use the pool first.Great. Whatever.
他们在这
They're here.
让他们进来
Let 'em in.
有点不爽
It's a little less than that.
冲个凉感觉很好
It's always nice to cool off.
这很冷
Ooh, it's cold out there.
楼上更暖和
It's warmer upstairs.
我们上楼
Let's go upstairs.
这是泰拉
This is tara.
快进来
Come on in.
到这来
Come here.
你好
Hello.
让我来看看我的女孩们在一起，来吧
Let me see my girls together, come on.
对，就这样，这就是我想看的
Yeah, that's right.That's what I wanna see.
我想看你们两个在一起
I wanna see the two of you together.
躺下
Just lie down.
吻他
Kiss him. Fucking kiss him.
吻他，来吧，宝贝
Fucking kiss him.Come on, baby.
现在是我想看的
Now this is what I wanna to see.
亲他
Kiss him. Kiss him more.
去他的下体
Go down on him.
不是你
No, no, no.Not you. Him.
去，杰瑞
Go, jerry.
你听我的，好吗？
You listen to me, okay?
谢谢
Thank you.
奇怪事情的结果，什么意思？
Strange how things work out.How do you mean?
我记得我喜欢过你，然后你跟泰拉在一起了
Well, I remember liking you,and then you ended up with tara.
我喜欢过克里斯蒂安
Then I remember liking christian,
他也跟泰拉在一起了
And he ended up with tara.
我不知道我能不能找到男朋友
I don't know if I'm gonna find a guy,
也许我需要离开这
Maybe I just need to get out of la.
这真是个相当糟糕的地方，不是吗？
Yeah, it's a pretty fucked-up town, isn't it?
当然你不想呆在这里，想在这吃午餐吗？
Sure you don't wanna stay, maybe grab some lunch?
我只想过来听听发生了什么
I just wanted to come by and hear what happened
亲自谢谢你
And to thank you in person.
这听起来像个奇怪的要求，但是我很感激
It sounded like a weird request, but I appreciate it.
你做了比我想的更多，谢谢
You took it a lot further than I thought. Thanks.
近些年我第一次小型演出
First acting gig I've had in years.
你真的爱泰拉？
You really love tara?
是，虽然我跟别人在一起，但是
Yeah. I mean, I'm with someone, but yeah.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
莱恩很久前我就放下了
Ryan, I let that go a long time ago.
你明白你也该放下，在某个时刻？
You realize that you have to let it go, too, at a certain point?
我知道
I know.
你为什么跟踪我？
Hey, hey, hey!Why are you following me?
你他妈在干什么？你想怎样？
What the fuck are you doing? What do you want, huh?
我不认识你
I don't know you!
我知道谁派你来的，承认吧
I know who sent you! Come on, admit it!
他妈的克里斯蒂安
Fucking christian!
你要我的照片？
You want my picture, huh?You want my picture?
你电话呢？
Where's your phone?Give it!
没人想要你的照片，好吗？
Nobody wants your picture, okay?
我知道，好吗？
I know, okay?
告诉克里斯蒂安我知道他做的鬼事
Tell christian I know what the fuck he's doing.
告诉他我知道
Tell that piece of shit I know!
搞什么？
What the fuck?
这不是我的电话
This can't be my phone.
操
Fuck.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我在找我的电话
I was just looking for my phone.
你找到了吗？
Did you find it?
克里斯蒂安，为什么我的电话在你的抽屉里
Christian, why is my phone in your drawer?
克里斯蒂安.你找到了吗？
Yeah, christian-did you find it?
克里斯蒂安，为什么我的电话.我知道你和莱恩的事
Christian, why was my phone--I know about you and ryan!
你个撒谎的婊子
You fucking lying bitch!
你打算承认吗？
Are you gonna fucking admit it? Are you?
Oh, shit! Are you gonna admit it
还是在我把你打出翔之后？
After I beat the fucking shit out of you?
你他妈的骗我
You fucking lied to me!
我相信你，你却骗我
I trusted you, and you lied to me!
克里斯蒂安...你撒谎
Christian...You lied!
求你了！我真的不知道你在说什么
Please! I really don't know what you're talking about!
天啊
Jesus!
上帝，我不相信我起得这么晚
Oh, my god, I can't believe how late I slept.
跑步怎么样？
How was your run?
宝贝，你怎么大早上喝龙舌兰？
Babe, why are you drinking tequila at noon?
莱恩
Ryan.
我很高兴你老板看精神病医生
I'm glad your boss is seeing a shrink.
我看了克里斯蒂安的计划
I've been looking at christian's schedule.
坎贝尔医生，三点
Dr. Campbell, 3:00.
你怎么知道坎贝尔是精神病医生
How do you know that dr. Campbell's a shrink?
够了，我谷歌他了
Stop it. I googled him.
你在干什么，保护这个精神病
What are you doing, protecting this psycho?
你为什么这么在意
Why do you even care?
因为他是个有病的混蛋
Because he's a sick fuck.
莱恩，我告诉，你不必喜欢他
Ryan, I told you, you don't have to like him. Wha--
这电影我不演了，吉娜
The movie's not gonna happen, gina.
我不知道你现在在说什么
I really don't know what you're talking about right now.
这电影我不演了
The movie's not--the movie's happening.
The movie's not gonna happen.
莱恩，乔恩做什么了？
Ryan, what did--okay, stop. What did jon--
不是乔恩不是杰拉尔德
It's not jon. It's not gerald.
也不是你，是他，是克里斯蒂安
It's not you. It's him. It's christian.
他不想让我演下去
He's not gonna let the movie happen.
你需要冷静，他要退出
You need to calm down. He's gonna pull out.
他要他妈的退出，你在说什么？
He's gonna fuckin' pull out.What are you talking about?
我不明白，什么？我不明白
I don't understand. What? I don't understand!
这电影不会有了因为我上了她女朋友
It's not gonna happen because I've been fucking his girlfriend
就在上月
For the last month.
这电影不会有了因为我爱她
It's not gonna happen because..I'm in love with her.
这就是为什么泰拉不再为这部电影工作
That's why tara stopped working on the movie.
我从来没告诉过你，我们住在一起一年了
I never told you this, but we lived together for a year.
我和泰拉
Me and tara.
她甩了我，然后傍上了克里斯蒂安
She dumped me when she started hooking up with christian.
我三年没见过她
I hadn't seen her in three years
直到那天我去试镜
Until that day I walked into the audition room,
再一次开始了
And then it started again.
克里斯蒂安发现了
And christian found out.
他跟踪我
He's had me followed,
他动了我的银行账户
He's fucked with my bank account,
他疯了，他知道我和泰拉
He's insane, and he knows about me and tara.
这就是原因，明白没？
That's why the movie's not gonna happen, okay? Got it?
我爱你，宝贝
I love you, baby.
你信任我
You believed in me.
你帮了我很多，但是我
You helped me so much,but I-- I can't control it,
无法控制我对她的感觉
How I feel about her.
但是她永远不会跟你在一起
But she'll never be with you.
她不打算回到你身边
She's not going back to that.
我们可以尽可能多的谈论这个
We can talk about this as much as you want.
我会花费整天时间
I'll spend all day talking about this,
然后我想要你离开这
And then I want you out of here.
我想你拿走所有你的东西
I want you to take all your things,
我想你离开这
And I want you out of here.
如后我去求克里斯蒂安
And then I'm going to beg christian
让这部电影继续
To keep the movie going.
我不在乎我有多贬低自己
I don't care how much I have to degrade myself.
我会求他让这部电影继续
I will beg him to keep the movie going.
我会确信你不在
And I will make sure that you are not
那里一百米的范围内
Within a hundred miles of that set
在拍摄期间
For the duration of the shoot.
通常我能控制自己
Usually I'm the one in control.
昨晚我没有
Last night I wasn't.
没有什么看起来真实
None of it seemed real.
不是当那个家伙替我口交
Not when that guy was sucking my dick
或者当泰拉试着让他上我
Or when tara tried to get him to fuck me.
这没有发生
Which didn't happen, fyi.
有一些确定的事情
There were certain things
泰拉和另一个女孩想要我们做
That tara and the other girl wanted us to do,
我甚至不知道我为什么在意
And I don't even know why I care.
就是一些我从没见过的网上认识的蠢孩子
Just some dumb kids on the internet I'll never see again.
就是...
Just...
不像我不受控制
Didn't feel like I wasn't in control.
我能具体感觉到
I felt objectified.
他们两个只是看着
The way the two of them just watched
告诉我们该怎么做
And told us what to do.
不常像那样被动
Doesn't usually go down like that.
通常是我控制大局
Usually I'm the one directing the scene.
这让我觉得像个演员
It made me feel like an actor.
有点像我在这里时的感觉
It's kinda like how I feel when I'm here.
你在这时你觉得你像个演员？
You feel like an actor when you are here?
我们都是演员，不是吗？我是说..
We're all actors, aren't we? I mean...
我们表现的不同
We all act differently,
取决于我们我们自身或周围的情况
Depending on the situation we're in or we're around.
当我跟你在一起时与我跟泰拉在一起时表现的不同
I don't act the same way with you as I do when I'm with tara.
就在昨晚和这里
Just last night and here...
证实了
Were pronounced,
那没有联系
That... Disconnect.
当你在这里时你担心变成一个演员吗？
So do you worry about being an actor when you're here?
我不会烦恼只是不喜欢
It doesn't worry me. I just don't like it.
我不喜欢感觉好像我不受控制
I don't like to feel like I'm not in control.
你有没有觉得来这是没有商量余地的
Have you processed that coming here is non-negotiable?
那是强制的
That it's mandatory?
你能接受吗？
Have you been able to accept that?
你是说我有没有想办法让我自己接受
You mean have I processed it?
我想是这样，我接受
I processed it. I've accepted it.
我只是不喜欢
I just don't like it.
每一天我都觉得什么事会发生
Every day I think what'll happen
如果我下周不去坎贝尔医生这儿
If I don't go back to dr. Campbell's next week.
这种想法总是出现在我的意识里
This thought is always on my mind.
答案是？
And the answer is?
如果我错过了一次谈话，你就会给讨厌的人打电话
If I miss a session,you will call the asshole.
讨厌的人是...我父亲
The asshole being...My father.
如果你告诉你父亲你没来治疗呢？
And if I told your father you're missing sessions?
那混蛋会拿走我的信托资金
Then the asshole will pull my trust fund if I miss a session.
你怎么想的？
What are you thinking?
我在想我在这时间足够长了吗？
I'm thinking have I been here long enough yet?
答案是？
And the answer is?
对，是我
Yeah, it's me.
你在那？我收到你的信息了
You there? I got your little message.
莱恩
Ryan, ryan, ryan.
可怜的莱恩
Poor, poor ryan.
这一切看起来相当刺激
It all seemed so exciting
当你18岁，那个摄影师找到你
When you were 18, and that photographer found you,
从密歇根一路直奔洛杉矶
Class trip from michigan, all the way out to los angeles.
对，好莱坞
Yeah, hollywood.
你突然远离
And you were suddenly so far away
那个你长大的地方
From that shithole town you grew up in,
你拍了一些照片
So you did
some modeling shoots.
每个人都很振奋
Everyone was so encouraging.
你甚至接了一两个商业广告
You even did a commercial or two.
我在Youtube看了一个你给普林格拍的广告
I saw one on youtube for pringles.
看起来真他妈的傻逼
Looked like a fucking moron.
然后呢？
Then what, huh?
没什么了
Nothing.
没什么
Nada.
你现在就是个酒吧招待偶尔去去小酒店
So now you're bartending with the occasional hotel gig
挣挣外快
To supplement your income.
导致了兰德尔想操你的X
That's just 'cause randall wants to fuck you up the ass.
谁知道？你也许让呢
Who knows?
You'd probably let him.
他可能已经上过你了
He probably has.
去年十月份在波斯特农庄酒店发生了什么？
What happened last October at the post ranch inn, huh?
你告诉吉娜了吗？
You tell gina about that?
我怀疑你告诉吉娜这次浪漫的旅行
I doubt you told gina about that romantic drive
一路沿海岸直到波斯特农庄酒店
All the way up the coast to the post ranch inn.
然后就是欺骗
And then bam!
你去年七月又跟泰拉联系了
You reconnect with tara last July.
然后又是欺骗
And then bam!
她说服每个人让你得到电影角色
She convinces everyone to cast you in a movie
你甚至连演戏都不会
You're not even capable of acting in.
又是欺骗
And then bam!
你上了我女朋友
You're fucking my girlfriend.
欺骗
And bam!
你说服辛西娅告诉每个人某个扯淡的故事
You convince cynthia to tell everyone some bullshit story.
那又怎样？
So what, huh?
你让泰拉甩了我？
You get tara to dump me?
你们难道要一起私奔？
So you guys can, what, run away together?
结婚
Get married?
你们难道可以
So you can, what,
和平共处在一间破屋子？
Coexist in some dump of a house somewhere?
想让泰拉回到那种生活？
Think tara's going back to that kind of life?
你觉得她会吗？
You think she's going to that lifestyle again?
你想听我的建议吗，莱恩
You want my advice, ryan?
回你的密歇根别再回来
Go back to michigan and get over it,
你这个愚蠢的傻X
You clueless little motherfucker.
你在这干什么？
What are you doing here?
我想和你谈谈
I just wanted to talk to you.
为什么？
Why?
莱恩
Ryan.
我完全不知道你们两个认识
I had no idea that you two knew each other.
世界真小啊
Interesting how small this town really is.
我不知道你在说什么？
I don't know what you're talking about.
别这样，宝贝，你的故事呢？
Come on, babe. Your little story?
什么故事？加州医院
What story? The ucla hospital.
一群人强奸了你
Bunch of guys running a train on you.
那孩子绝不够聪明
There's no way that kid's smart enough
竟然自己想出了这些
To come up with that on his own.
但是我知道那是谁
But I know somebody who is.
我该怎么做？
What was I supposed to do?
它有效了，宝贝
It worked, babe.
你想引起我的注意，你做到了，我在这
You wanted my attention, and you got it. Here I am.
过来，自作聪明的人
Come here, smarty pants.
我不生气，我觉得这很有趣
I'm not mad. I thought it was cute.
对不起，没关系
I'm sorry.  It's okay.
你真的觉得我需要给女孩吃迷幻药吗？
Did you really think I would need to slip a girl a roofie?
不
No.
我感兴趣的是
What I am interested in...
你们怎么认识的
Is how you guys know each other.
那不重要
Oh, it doesn't matter.
但是我好奇，你们怎么遇见的？
Yeah, but I am curious. How'd you meet?
你喜欢他吗？
Do you like him?
你跟他做过吗？他鸡鸡大吗？
Have you fucked him? Has he got a big dick?
是...我在泰拉之前遇见他
Okay, yes, I... I met him
before he knew tara.
我们一起上表演课
We had the same acting class together.
是，我们交往了，然后他遇见了她
And yes, we had a thing, and then he met her,
然后就结束了
And then it was over.
非常有趣
Very interesting.
有趣？
Interesting?
真的？
Really?
为什么？
Why?
为什么这对你这么重要
And why does it even matter to you anymore?
你觉得她在干什么？
What did you think she was doing?
我是说，我不知道，她和他在一起大概一年
I mean, I don't know, she dated him for like a year or so,
然后她甩了他
And then she dumped him.
从那之后我们就没怎么见过
We didn't know each other very well back then.
我是说，我们去了几个相同的派对
I mean, we went to like a few of the same parties,
我觉得我们跟一些同样的人约会
And I think we dated a few of the same guys,
但是我们真的不再是朋友
But we weren't really friends or anything.
然后她遇见了你
And then she met you.
克里斯蒂安？
Christian?
克里斯蒂安，你在干什么？
Christian, what are you doing?
嗨？
Hello?
克里斯蒂安？
Christian?
克里斯蒂安，搞什么？
Christian, what the fuck?
克里斯蒂安！不要！
Christian! No! No!
接电话
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
你怎么不接呢？
Why don't you fucking answer?
快他妈的接电话
Pick up the fucking phone!
无法相信你对她做的，老兄
Can't believe what you did to her, dude.
你是个恶心的混蛋
You are one sick fuck.
辛西娅？
Cynthia?
嗨
Hi.
你去哪了
Where were you?
坎贝尔医生那
Dr. Campbell's.
你干什么？
What's that?
嗯...
Um...
我要离开了，行吗？
I'm gonna leave, okay?
我要跟我姐姐呆在圣塔芭芭拉一段时间
I'm gonna go stay with my sister in santa barbara for a bit.
今早我很抱歉
I'm sorry about this morning.About...
每一件事我都抱歉
About everything.
我知道,我知道，我也对不起
Yeah, I know. I know. I'm sorry, too.
但是无论如何我要走了
But I'm gonna leave anyway.
我需要听到你答应
I just-- I need to hear that you're okay with it.
我想知道你答应我离开
I wanna know that you're okay with me going.
求你了
Please.
你能让我走吗？
Will you please just let me go?
我爱你
I loved you.
我真的爱你
I really... Loved you.
用我自己的方式，但是我爱你
In my own way, but I loved you.
我知道
I know, I know.
我也爱你
I loved you, too.
但是我需要考虑一些事情
But I-- I just need to think about things.
我需要听你说你答应放我走
And I need to hear you say that it's okay if I go.
好
It's okay.
我会答应
I'll be fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
我需要你点东西
I need something from you.
任何，告诉我
Yes, anything. Tell me.
你需要什么？
What do you need?
一个不在场证明
An alibi.
什么？
Wha... What?
什么不在场证明？
For what?
这个下午
This afternoon.
我不明白，下午发生什么了？
I-I don't understand. What happened this afternoon?
你去了
You went to...
你刚说你去坎贝尔医生那
You just said you went to dr. Campbell's.
你干什么了，还发生什么了？
What did you-what else happened?
跟辛西娅有关
Something happened to cynthia.
克里斯蒂安
Christian...
克里斯蒂安发生什么了？
Christian, what happened?
这不重要
It's not important.
我不...发生什么了？
Uh, I don't--what happened?
我不明白
I don't get--I don't understand.
你说发生一些事情什么意思
What do you mean,something happened?
我三点五十五离开坎贝尔医生那
I left dr. Campbell's at 3:55.
四点二十回家
Got here at 4:20.
你一直跟我在一起
You've been with me ever since.
明白吗？
Do you understand?
宝贝，点点头
Nod for me, baby.
点头
Nod for me.
还有一件事
One more thing.
如果你再去见他
If you ever see him again,
如果他联系你
If he ever contacts you,
如果他给你打电话
If he calls you,
如果你们还在同一件屋子
If you're even in the same room together...
我就杀了他
I will kill him.
看着我
Look at me.
我会杀了他并会想办法逃脱
I will kill him, and I will get away with it.
明白？
You understand?
是
Yes.
点点头，宝贝
Nod for me, baby.
点头
Nod for me.
好，好
Okay, okay.
这才是好女孩
That's a good girl.
好女孩
Good girl.
所以你们刚从迪拜回来
So, you guys just got back from dubai.
是，我们住在帆船酒店
Yeah, we stayed at the burj al arab.
我觉得你在迪拜的经历很糟糕？
I thought you had a bad experience at the burj?
觉得你只是呆在亚特兰蒂斯
Thought you were only staying at the atlantis now?
是，但是泰拉从没去过迪拜
Yeah, but tara had never been to dubai,
我觉得这对她很有趣
So I thought it'd be fun for her.
这对我不重要，我一整天都要开会
It didn't matter to me. I was in meetings all day.
迪拜怎么样？你在那做什么了？
So how was dubai? What'd you do there?
你知道，就是购物，花钱
You know, just shopped, laid out.
你做过电影方面的工作？
Weren't you working on a movie?
是，有点
Yeah, uh, kind of.
你怎么知道
Yeah. How'd you know?
我们有共同的朋友，谁？
We have a friend in common. Who?
克里斯蒂安
Christian.
你曾经跟他交往过？
Didn't you used to go out with him?
是
Yeah.
他又在做另一部电影我的一个朋友在里面
He's producing another movie a friend of mine is in,
杰登告诉我你和克里斯蒂安曾经住在一起
And jaden told me that you and christian used to live together
当我今晚见到你，我就把所有的信息都汇总到一起了
And when I met you tonight, I just put it all together.
是，克里斯蒂安和我大概交往了一年
Yeah, christian and I went out for about a year.
当我们分手时
And then when we broke up,
我决定不再参与电影
I decided to take myself off the film.
对不起，分手让你很伤心吗？
Oh, I'm sorry.Was the breakup that bad?
不，一点也不
No. No, not at all.
不，只是，有些事还在继续
No, it's just, there were a lot of things going on and--
等等
Wait, wasn't that--
是当那个女孩被杀的那段时间吗?
Was that around the time when that girl was killed?
克里斯蒂安的瑜伽老师或者别的什么事？
Christian's yoga instructor or something?
是，实际上...
Yeah, actually...
是，是那段时间我们分手的
Yeah, it was right around that time that we broke up, yeah.
他们没发现凶手是谁，对吗？
They never found out who did that, did they?
没，我意思是，他们找到一些嫌疑人
No. I mean, they had some suspects,
除此之外，没有了
But aside from that, no.
最后什么也没发现
At the end, nothing.
他们不是在某人助手的车里发现一把刀吗？
Didn't they find like a knife in the car of someone's assistant?
是，但是，我听说
Yeah, but... I mean, I heard that it was basically
无论是谁杀了人
Whoever killed the person, her,
肯定会把刀扔进他的车里
Must have thrown it in his car.
我意思是，我那晚跟他在一起，所以不是他，但是
I mean, I was with him that night, so it wasn't him, but--
是，在那之后
Yeah, after that...
所以他们没抓到任何人？
So they never arrested anybody?
没有，他们没有
No. Actually, no, they didn't.
太可怕了
That's so scary.
是
Yeah.
顺便问一下，克里斯蒂安怎么样？
How is christian doing, by the way?
克里斯蒂安他很好
Christian, he's, um, he's good.
我们没有过多的交谈
We don't really talk that much,
除了短信和脸书之类的
Aside from texts and facebook and stuff.
但是上次我收到他的信距离现在很近
But the last time I heard from him was pretty recent,
他很棒
And he's doing great,actually.
去一下洗手间，马上回来
Gonna go to the ladies' room. I'll be right back.
很好，你们很开心
Good, good. I'm glad you guys had a good time.
她很棒，伙计，是
She's cute, man.Yeah, she's cute.
嗨，是我
Hey! It's me.
对，我现在和她在一起
Yeah, I'm here with her right now.
我们先喝点东西
Yeah, we went to david's place first for drinks.
你想让我做什么？
So... What do you want me to do?
任何你想要我问她的
Anything you want me to ask her
除了你要我问的之外
Besides what you already told me to?
她看起来很高兴，但是她好像是装的
She seems happy, even though she's like totally faking it.
喂？
Hello?
喂，莱恩
Hello, ryan.
喂，莱恩，在吗？
Hello, ryan, are you there?